Hello everyone, I am Samantha from Cloud Shanghai.
Today, I will give you a live broadcast of the new 5.2 function.
After you install the software, you will find that many of our tools seem to be gone.
But in fact, it is not gone, but it is a tool group function after 5.2.
For example, like our edit version tool.
We often press down to find that the tools related to the point line edit are all integrated in it.
If we want to go back to the previous old version of a tool layout mode.
Then we come to the user self-identification setting.
Then we come to the user interface.
We can see that there is a tool group.
After we turn off this button, we can go back to the previous old version of a tool layout mode.
Now what I want to talk about is our storage file storage.
This is an update on the tool layout.
When we click on the file and then save the project file,
it will save a project file and a tool layout.
Now we have an update on this tool layout.
The original tool layout is a tool layout with only one view.
Now we can save a tool layout with four views.
All we need to do here is to set it up in the settings.
We come to the user self-identification.
Then in the default file.
There is a shortcut to save four angles.
After we select this option,
we can save the shortcut to save four angles.
Now we close the window.
Then we come to our next tool,
which is our sticker classification tool.
We first select the sticker on our background.
Then the attribute editor.
We can see that there is a classification.
Click on the box.
There are three types of a sticker classification.
Then we choose a logo classification here.
Then we can also come to our front.
Make a self-defined classification.
For example, here we delete this.
Enter the four-wings print on the classification list.
Next, what I want to talk about is a function update on our quick photo.
Then we come to our quick photo 3D window.
Let's save a quick photo first.
Then we save a quick photo.
We can do a single quick photo or multiple.
Then here we can make a setting of a view or a self-defined view.
Then on the left, we can set the size of a picture.
On the right, we can set the number of displays.
Then here we have the largest number.
Now it can reach 10.
Then in the following options,
there is an option to save HTML files.
After clicking on it,
it will save a quick photo of an HTML file.
Then we open this HTML file before.
Then we click Next.
Then we can switch to the next quick photo.
Then what I'm talking about is an update on our video.
Then our other options are unchanged.
It's just that there's one more option below the duration.
That's our save HTML file.
After saving it,
the duration will turn gray.
This is because the saved HTML file is a fixed rotation picture.
It can be used to make GIFs or web-based rotation videos.
Now let's click on our record button to record.
After recording,
click Save to save the file.
Here,
I'll show you a saved HTML file.
After saving,
we can save an AVI.
We can save an AVI and an HTML file.
Click Next,
you can see the next picture.
Then what I'm going to talk about is a mode that we just released,
which is our material list mode.
Then we come to our window,
right upper corner of the model.
Click on it,
you can switch to the material list mode at the bottom.
After switching,
the page will open a BOM editor.
Here,
we can see the size of the fabric,
the volume of the material,
and its price.
The volume of the material used for this fabric is determined by the placement of the sheet in the flower arrangement.
Then we come to the flower arrangement mode.
Then we click on the upper right corner of the window.
You can see that we have a BOM editor that can be opened.
Then we can open our BOM editor in other modes.
When we do a initialization arrangement,
we can see it.
Click on the update of our BOM editor.
Then we can see that the volume of the material will change.
Then we click on the setting button on the currency unit.
You can switch our currency unit.
For example,
I changed it to RMB CNY.
Here,
find CNY.
Then,
close the button.
You can see that the currency unit has been changed to RMB CNY.
Here,
close the button.
Then close the window.
Our currency unit will be changed.
Then we can choose a different color.
Do an edit.
And then,
it will show the cost of the current color and the total cost of all colors.
The price below can also be changed.
And the number of units length can also be changed.
Including the unit length,
it can also be changed.
For example,
it can be changed to inches,
or centimeters,
millimeters,
and so on.
Next to it,
it will show its cost.
Below,
it will show its total price.
Here,
we can see its total cost.
And this content will appear in our Closet process list.
Next,
I'm going to talk about some AVT files that we use on our virtual models.
That is,
we see these rectangular objects on this window,
and we can see that these are the original objects.
Then,
where do we open these files?
We just need to open our AVT folder.
There is a 3D shape folder.
Open it,
it is the AVT file that we made of these envelopes.
Next,
we will make an arrangement for it.
We open the virtual model editor,
open the arrangement page,
and then add an arrangement board.
Adjust the size of the arrangement board,
so that it can adapt to the AVT file of this envelope.
Next,
I will adjust the position of this arrangement board.
In this way,
our arrangement board and arrangement point are installed.
Turn off the editor,
and then we open our arrangement point.
We can do the same as we usually do in clothing,
to arrange our board to this AVT file,
which is convenient for our production.
In order to adapt to more envelopes,
the AVT file of our envelopes can be transformed.
We just need to select this AVT file,
and then come to our main folder,
and then we can see the arrangement board.
We can see a specification,
and it will display the size of XYZ.
We remove the fixed proportion,
and then we can modify its size one by one.
We can also click on the icon in the upper right corner of the arrangement board,
and switch it to a transform arrangement board,
and then perform a transformation of an AVT file,
or a modification of an envelope.
After the transformation,
we can switch to an ordinary arrangement board.
And we can see that after the transformation,
part of it goes to the bottom of the grid.
We can select,
we perform a mobile virtual model to the ground,
and then we can move our AVT file to the bottom of our grid.
Next,
I'm going to talk about an update on our copper model.
First, let's take a look at our copper model.
It has added 6 to 18 months of children model.
Then we double-click to open it.
This child model is added to our window.
Then we come to see our size file folder.
Double-click to open the corresponding model file folder.
Double-click to open.
There will be a copper model size of different months.
Then we also double-click to open it,
and we can apply it directly.
Or you can directly do a virtual model editing in the virtual model editor.
Our model can also make a change to its shoes.
Find a file folder that corresponds to a model shoe.
Then click to open the shoes inside.
You can apply it.
It's the same with our other models.
Next, I'm going to talk about an update on our aluminum model.
Previously, our aluminum model posture
was divided into a posture of wearing high heels and flat shoes.
Now we're not doing this anymore.
We just click to open it.
And then choose to keep the posture of the shoes now.
Click to confirm.
Then his posture will make a normal change.
If we don't hook this option,
His foot will become a flat shoe.
Then we just have to open the posture again,
and hook this option.
He will become a normal high heel.
And now.
If we make a shoe change,
is no longer required to carry out a change of posture
as long as we directly open our flat bottom shoes
its posture will automatically carry out a change
that now we come to talk about is that our V2 model
now can also carry out a show
that we open a costume
and then we come to our animation mode
and then we come to the next
to open our V2 folder
and then open our motion folder
and then open our motion
that the front of the two options is default
click OK
and then we can move our perspective
and then drag our bottom of the real speed
can look at our model of a show of action
and then we can move our perspective
and then we can drag our perspective
after looking at the real speed
we can drag the real speed
and then click record
can start to perform this show of the record
that because it takes some time to record the show
that here I will not have finished such a recording
so now I will turn off the recording
and then we will change this position to the original position
and then switch a mode
I will explain the shape of our 3D window
a function update on the 3D window
that in 5.2
our 3D window
the biggest update
is that we have added a 3D window
a function of real-time rendering
that now I open a costume
and then in the upper left corner of the 3D window
there is a high-quality rendering button
when we click on it
the costume will show
only when rendering
to have a texture
we can see
the whole fabric texture
will look more like a real costume
and a real costume
that we can
open a high-quality rendering
after 3D quick photo
so that you can get a better quality
of a quick photo
but then we
rendering function
rendering high-quality pictures
or there is a certain gap
that we look at the three of the difference
that the left side is a normal quick photo
that the middle is to open a high-quality rendering
high-quality rendering after the quick photo
that the right side is a rendering function
rendering out of
a
high-quality rendering
that we can see
the real-time rendering of the quick photo effect
is obviously more than the normal picture
there is still a certain difference
so
high-quality pictures
it is recommended to use rendering
that in our previous 3D window
when
some of the lace fabric
may have a transparent effect
just like now
is that the two layers of fabric will be transparent
you can not see which layer
inside which layer outside
and its through will be very strange
that when we open this three high-quality rendering after
that this problem will also be solved
we can clearly see it
this lace fabric it is
on top of this one on top of the sand
that here is our high-quality rendering of a function update
that next is our quick simulation mode above a update
that our simulation mode open after
you can see that there are now three models
one is a fast one is a normal speed is a
that the missing it is that our simulation
is completed
is our animation is now complete
because it is only applied to our
on the show so
it will be moved to our show mode above
that we can see here
this animation completed a simulation mode
that the model model between the old and new version
of a name of the changes and
its one of the four modes of a detailed introduction to it
will be displayed on our official website
that you can see
that here
on the left is our old version of a name
on the right is our new version of the simulation model of a name
you can see before and after it
its changes and its corresponding
on the right is a corresponding function of their introduction
that I would like to mention next
is that our default variable of the physical properties
of a change
we originally a curve intensity and so on
of the data to carry out a new change
now it will become more soft
that I want to talk to you next
is that some of the new features of our 2D window
that first I want to talk about
our function update in the parallel open edit
we open a costume
then we choose our edit tool
to our 2D window
we can see it on the right in front of
the line I can see the section
we can go directly to the
adjustment to open a parallel edit of the pattern
a section
and then we simulate
we can see the front end to open
that we are line to our back
as we are in the upper right of the horizontal line
we can click
right click work to connect the point of connects to the point of pointing line
to
Then we can delete this index line
Then we can also click on the right button
Do a deselect link
Then our symmetrical version of DXF
It's in our software
It's also in this state
How can you set this version as one
A state of symmetrical opening and editing
Then we just need to choose our hook outline tool
Then select its middle line to make a cut
Then delete half of it
Next, select its middle line again
Then right-click to do a symmetrical opening and editing
Then this version will become
A state of symmetrical opening and editing
Finally, we will make a cut and sew
It can be cut while opening our version
Combine it together
What's next
What I want to explain is our basic line
Creation and editing functions
In the old version
Our basic line
It is not possible to do
One edit and create
But after 5.2
We can all do an edit and create
Then we come to the front four menu on the left side of the 2D window
There is a new added lock
Then we can use our edit version tool
To select our basic line
After selecting
We can edit it
For example, we select the basic line
Then right-click to select the segment
Then we can do this
A segment of the basic line
Then we can also select our basic line
One move
Or a Carve
You can even make it a different length
Then we can lack its length
Change it to 300mm
Then we can also
Select our basic line
Create aカキ
Run our canvass to create an intuition line
Create a guideline
Then next
I want to talk about
How to prioritize our basis line
Before talking
I want to talk about the difference between the basic line and the inner line first
The inner line is for us
In the software, it is designed and can change the 3D shape of the costume
And add some details
For example, the fold line, the line of the face, the fold of the face, and so on
The base line mainly acts as a marker
For example, our chest line, waist line, and hip line
These lines
Now I want to be on the front of this group
To draw our line
Before drawing
I want to cut my face shape into a grid
Convenient for everyone to see the changes in our grid
Then we cancel it
Next, let's choose our internal multidirectional tool
Because our internal line
It will have a grid effect on our board
Now I draw an internal line
You can see
In my completion
At the same time
Our grid
Our grid is going to make a change
And we choose our board
You can check its grid number on your computer
Found that its grid number is 1566
Then the original grid number is 155966
Then the original grid number is 1559
So the number of our two grids will change
That is to say, our internal line will have an impact on the grid
Then I will draw a base line next
Then I will draw a base line
You can see that the base line is across our grid
It has no effect on the grid
And I choose the board
You can find that the number of grids has not changed
Then I switch to the black and white surface
You can see
The red one is our internal line
The blue one is our base line
So the color can be divided into these two lines
Then I'm going to take these two lines
And we're going to delete them
And before we delete them
I want to mention that
Because our internal line will not change the grid
So we suggest that when designing
You can use the base line first
And then we'll call it the internal line
In this way
Its speed will be faster
Okay, now I'm going to draw our base line
That is to say, the single machine starts and the double machine ends
What about its drawing method
We draw the same internal line
The single machine starts
Press the control key
The left button is to enter our point of projection
The left button is the point of projection
And then
Press the release button
Release the control key
The left button is the straight line
So that we can establish our base line
Now I'm going to talk about our G-shaped base line tool
Press it down
You can choose our G-shaped base line tool
Then we can drag the left button to draw our base line
Then we can also press the left button
And then enter the specific value
To draw our G-shaped base line
Then we can also use our multidirectional base line tool
To draw our base line of a certain length
We right-click
You can enter the length of this line
Press the return button
You can complete the length of this line
You can complete the drawing of the line
Then we click on the circular base line
You can draw a circular base line on it
We enter a specific value
When our base line is just finished
It is in a locked state
After we unlock it
We can select our base line
Do an edit
For example, we move its position
Or do a contraction
And stretch
We can also rotate this base line
After we finish drawing the base line
We can choose our G-shaped base line tool
To categorize it as a part of the line
Then categorize it as a plate
In this way
Our one pocket is done
Then next
What I want to tell you is
One update on our function
Then we open a new costume
After opening the costume
You also know
The function of this line
Is to use our edit board tool
Then click on the right-click button
Select add line
Enter the specific value
You can create a line
This line
Is to directly dig this line
Is our style
Become a lock style
I open the pressure map now
Look at the skirt
We can see this skirt
Its hip is tighter
Now we have a function
This is the extension board
It can be added at the same time
The extension board
Maintain our waist
Then the amount of the waist is increased
Then we click on the right-click button
After adding a line
There will be an extension board
And add a line
Then we first determine the direction of the line
Then it is the width of the line
Next is the length of the line
We come to the back
We also focus on the board
Then right-click on it
You can make a width and length
A specific number of a set
Click to confirm
The extension will increase
Then we click on the simulation
Then you can see
Now this skirt
The volume of the waist
It's getting loose
Then its waist
There is no change
This skirt will become more harmonious
Then next
What I want to talk about
Is one of our extension functions
Let's take a look
At our front
First of all
I'm going to choose its one
Shoe length
Then click on the right-click button
There will be a rotation
A selection of the line
After selecting
We click on a starting point of the line
Then choose a direction of the line
Next is the transfer of a line
Then click
Then confirm our length
Then
Our line
Will be established
Will be transferred
Then we click on the model
Then you
That way
Our embroidery
It's turned into our chest
This is the update on our function
Then next
I'm going to talk about
A tool we just started
Extend the line
It can be
Estimated
Under our line
Extend the board
First, let's
Come to our 2D window
Then
We choose our extension board
Long press
There will be an extension board line
And we first set the first section of the length line
Then select the second section of line
Basic line
Semi that side of where we can set extension direction
following that direction
We can set the length of the extension
Above is the length line
It's the line that we set in the first paragraph
Below is the basic line
Which describes our second section of wire
We can
Fing хочет set one of the extensions
Or to set a extension
Or set the length of the extension
Then here I choose the length of the extension
Is the distance of movement
Then I extend the basic line section to 150 mm
The direction can be selected as the direction of the end of the line
Or extend it on both sides
Then here I choose the direction of the start line
Extend and click to confirm
Then this version can be extended
Then we come to the back
Okay, let's simulate it
Then you can see
The amount of this cross section will be much more than before
Then here I will adjust its lower plate on the side
it is good
Then we can see
The cross section of this back piece is done
Then below
If we think that the amount of the interlacing is not enough
Then we can
Make a merge of this board
Then remove it from the interlacing
Then I want to talk about the function update of the extension board point
What about this function?
We originally chose to do only one extension on one side
Now we just click on the extension line in the middle
Can be extended at both ends at the same time
Okay, let's click on it on the left
You can determine an extension like this
Then I will simulate it again
We can see it now
This one
The amount of the interlacing will be more
Then what we are going to talk about is our extension function
Then first we come to the 2D window
Then this one is also our new tool
We choose our extension tool
Then first we set the line of our extension
After setting it, a window will pop up
We can choose to set the extension type
Then below
You can set the number of extensions
Here I choose four extensions
Then the next one is the width
Width is the width of the extension
Start and end
The two are indicated by the width of the beginning of the line
And the width of the end of the extension
Then set the proportion of it
After writing it, you can make a single width change
Then when I change its width
You can see our 2D window
The board will also follow a change
Then we can preview the shape of this board
The following extension is the extension between the fold and the cut
The same as above
Can be fixed proportionally
You can also change it one by one
Then the following is to create a cutout
To create a cutout
We can add a cutout at the end
You can also choose the opening
On the top
Make an extension of the cutout
Or both ends
Then click OK
Then our board
There will be a cutout like this
And our board
It can be automatically sealed
We don't need to seal it again
Let's rearrange it
Then make a hardening of our board
Make the shape of its cutout better
Click to simulate
Next, let's solve the hardening
We will simulate the following
That such a cutout is done
Do you think it's very easy?
Then we can pull it open
You can see the effect of this cutout
After our insulation is lighted
The effect of this cutout will be more obvious
You can see
The effect of our cutout
You can see it corresponds to our 3D circle
Here is the effect of our cutout
This is our board lock function
Now we are in the 2D window
On the left side
There will be a lock menu
You can carry out the board outside the line inside the line
Basic line and so on
Some lock
Here
First I lock our board outside the line
We can find that we can choose the inside line
But we can't choose our board outside the line
All boards can't be selected
Next we lock the board outside the line
Inside the line
Then our inside line becomes gray
We can't make another selection
But our board can be selected
Next, our basic line is default
Is a locked state
After unlocking
We can choose our basic line
Next is the instruction line
First, let's generate the instruction line
We first use our tag
To generate our instruction line
Then we lock the instruction line
After that
We can't move the instruction line anymore
When we unlock the lock
We can move this instruction line
And do an edit or delete
In addition to locking the whole
We can also lock one
Then we right click
You can see here
There will be a lock option
It is actually corresponding to our lock menu
Now we are doing a single line
And the lock of the point
For example, the embroidery
After we select
Right click
You can choose our lock
Then our point line will be locked
I can't select anymore
But other points and lines
Can be selected
Then we can also select
One board
Lock
After locking
The board can no longer be selected
And edit
But other boards
Can be selected
And edit
To unlock
You only need to right click
Select to unlock all
To unlock
You only need to right click
Select to unlock all boards
Then
The lock just now
Will be removed
The same as the internal line
You can select a single internal line
Lock
The lock will turn gray
Then the other internal lines
Can be selected
But this internal line
Can't be selected anymore
And the same as the blank
Right click
You can remove all
One lock of the internal line
Then select open
Then select the window
Next
We'll talk about the bottom line
The bottom line
Will perform a
After unlocking
We can do a single lock
For the bottom line
After locking
The bottom line
Can't be selected anymore
But other
Bottom lines
Can be selected
Okay, so what's next?
This is our one
A description of a function that is locked
So what's next?
It's a function description of our rotation logo
So first of all
Let's choose our edit focus tool
We can do one for our logo
Make a rotation
It's in a horizontal state
Rotate into a state of our number
Okay, so this is our logo
A small update on the function
So what's next?
What I'm talking about is our one
Group function
Board group function
What about this function?
For editing multi-layer clothing
Like down jacket, cotton suit
Or multi-layer dress
It's a very convenient tool
So first of all, let's go to our 2D window
Put our front
The front of the front of the loud surface board
Select to make a group setting
And then what's next?
Select our loud and layered board
Make a group of one
Set and our embroidered board
Make a group setting
After the setting
We just need to select a board
You can select
Or for us like a language service
We are convenient for us
For the table of the board
Unite to make a pressure value adjustment
Okay, and our layer board
What about the corresponding pressure value?
It also needs to be adjusted accordingly
So if we want to select a single board
What to do
We just need to select this board
Then click on it again
You can select this single board
This is the tool group function
Then what I'm going to talk about is our
Change the length of the board
The function update on this tool
First of all, let's select our 2D window
The tool to compare the length of the board
You have to select our sleeves
You have to select our front
Make a length comparison
Then we can be in one of the points
Right click
Then click on it again
Then there is one more option
It's called moving the board to the intersection point
So after we select this
The sleeve board will move to the intersection point of the board when you click on it
What about this function?
It's convenient for us to draw a continuous line between the two boards
For example, we're going to draw a continuous one on the front of this sleeve
To be separated
Before we draw a line
Because I'm drawing the front now
But the front is now at the bottom of the sleeve
If you draw a line directly
It will be built on this sleeve board
So in order to avoid this situation
I'm going to adjust the order of my front
Then put it in the front
After putting it in the front
Let's choose our multidirectional basic line tool
Then to carry out a separation line of a drawing
After we draw this separation line
Let's choose our sleeve board again
In the same way
Let's change it in order
Put it in the front
Then put it in the front with my change
Then use our basic line tool
To draw our separation line
The two separation lines are a relationship of excessive change
After we draw it
How do we turn the board over?
We just have to choose our sleeve
Right click on the top
Rotate
Then choose X to go
Then choose his sleeve line
You can turn it around
What about the following
I will choose one of my colloidal contours
Then cut it into a seam
Then we can see
This board will be cut
Let's simulate
You can see this separation line in the 3D window
Then what I'm going to talk about next
It's a update of our sewing line
We have a sewing line
A function of a sewing line
Then select the sewing line
Come to the attribute editor
There is a sewing line below the 3D sewing line
Then select the open button
Then you can see that there is another kind of sewing line
After we select
Then click open
Then we can see
This hair line sticker will be opened
Then we come to the 3D window to see
We are now left and right
A seam effect
It's not the same
The left side is a seam effect of hooking in
Then our right side
This is a bulge
A seam effect
By changing the hair line sticker
You can switch to a different one
A seam effect of sewing line
What I'm going to talk about next
Is our sticker code tool
Then we come to the back of our sticker
Then select our code tool
Select the edge of our sticker
Then we come to the attribute editor
You can enter specific numbers to enter the code
That's here for convenience
Specific numbers to enter the code
I can use my express key directly
My direction key to enter a code
I put this sticker out quickly
Then I change the number of different numbers
You can see different numbers below
This is a code effect of a sticker
Now I go back to my home
This is our sticker code function
What I'm going to talk about next is our color search function
Then we select the fabric of our jacket
Then come to our color
The right side is our color library
Now there will be a search bar below
We just need to enter the name of the color
Press back to search for the corresponding color
Click to confirm to apply the color
What I'm going to talk about next is a change in our sticker type
We select the edge of our sleeve
Then select its sticker
Do a whole sticker
After the sticker we can see
Its preview content will change
Click to pull the frame
We can see that there is a different type of sticker
We can use different parts
Choose a different type of sticker
Different type of stickers
Will cause a different physical shape
I'll simulate it now
Then I switch to a different type of sticker
For example, this sticker is a harder sticker
We can see the change in the edge of the box
Then change to a softer sticker
So this is a function update of our sticker
What I'm going to talk about next is our
A function update of our 3D zipper
Then open a new costume
Then our 3D zipper
Originally can only be established in the 3D window
Now our 3D zipper
Can be established in 2D
The operation method is the same as before
Click
Then we click on the simulation
Then our zipper will automatically pull up
And we can see it appears
Then we turn off the simulation
Then pull its zipper down
Click on the simulation again
Then it will open on it
You can see the upper zipper
This zipper is our new update content
Then we can do
In the 3D editor
You can pull the zipper
And our upper and lower zippers
A sample
Make a modification
We change a different type
Change its upper and lower zippers
The following
We can now also pull the zipper
And the zipper
Make a separate material attribute
A change
We just need to close it
Choose the same material
Then I can change
For example, I turn the zipper
Into a metal material
Then I pull the zipper
Change its material
Become a plastic material
Then choose color
Here
I applied it to it
A color similar to the sound
You can see
A change in our zipper
Then pull the zipper
I also put its material type
Give it a metal material
Then you can see
We have such a zipper
It's already a completely independent
A material modification
Then I want to talk about
Is our chain function
Our chain function
The same as the zipper
Is to be able to carry out
A creation of a 2D window
Then we directly
The method is the same as before
Single start
Double end
Then you can see
Our chain
Will be created
Then next
Let's talk about the side
The side is also a new addition
Next
Let's talk about the side
The side is also a new addition
The creation function of the 2D window
The creation method is the same as before
The same
Then we will create a single machine at the bottom
Start
Then go back to the original point
Then click again
Then such a
The side will be created
Let's simulate
This side will be sewn to our skirt
On the bottom
What I'm going to talk about next
Is the update of our chain function
Everyone knows
We have two types of names
Our default name is
Our OBJ name
Then we can add a real name
The original we only have
On the line name and free name
There is OBJ name on it
Now
We are in this sewing line
Name line
Can also make this OBJ name line
Then we are in the front here
Use the sewing line name
To increase this OBJ name line
default is an OBJ name line option
Here
I put this name line
A rough draft
Change it a little
You can see it more clearly
Then come to the side
You can see
This is a three-dimensional
An OBJ name line
That's what we are
A update on this name line
Is our sewing line name line
Also has the function of OBJ name line
That's all
About us
A function update on the material
What I'm going to talk about next
The last one
Is our
An update on our sewing line
First of all
I will tell you
Is our
A update on our sewing line background
Let's go to our
Sewing window
Then we click on the sewing line
The detailed friends
May find
Our background now
Is a picture
It's actually a picture
Originally our background
Can only be pure background
Now we can use the picture
Then we can see
The text in the picture attribute
We click to open
A change
We can change
To a different background
A background
Next we can
Change the color
We can
Go to
Add a different color
This color
Is directly covered
On this background
Above
And we
In the lamp
There will be
A ground shadow
Option
When we
Hook
Then
We can see
This model
It will be
There will be
A shadow
At the foot
That makes
The model
Will be more real
We
Turn off the transparency
After
The shadow
Will still be preserved
We
Open again
Transparency
Now
Our text
Is able to
Self-designed
A text
Is our
Self-designed
Picture background
Here
I choose
A picture of myself
Then
Open
This picture
Will be
In the form of stretching
Applied to
Our
So
To avoid
The picture
We can
Change the size
Of the
Portrait
Is the same
Size
So that
When we
Do it again
This
Portrait
Will not
Be
Transformed
Then
This
Is about
Our
Update
On the background
Then
Next
Let's talk about
Our
Hair
Transformation
After
5.2
We
Open
Our
Transparency
Then
For the
Convenience
I
This
Hair
A
Color
It
Changed
To
A
Red
Then
Next
We
Pull
Down
We
Can
See
There
Is
A
Hair
Transformation
Then
We
Click
The green
Then
We
Click
The top
Color
And
Use
A
Blue
At
This
Time
You
Can
See
This
Hair
Is
A
Rainbow
Transformation
In
The
Middle
We
Can
Use
To
Adjust
The
Color
Range
The
Middle
Position
Is
Smaller
Then
The
Start
Of
The
Middle
Color
Will
Go
Down
To
The
Top
Position
Then
The
Top
Color Range
Is Very
Convenient
We
Use
Directly
To
Drag
This
Pull
It
Can
Make
A
Adjustment
Then
Can
Achieve
A
Different
Color
Effect
With
Such
A
Function
We
Can
Have A
Lighting
Function
Then
I
Want
To
Talk
About
One
Lighting
Radiance
Function
A
Update
After
You
Install
5.2
Will
Find
We
5.2
More
A
Lighting
Maybe
Everyone
Will
Be
A bit
Just
Suspect
These
Lightings
Don't
Know
How
To
Use
Today
I
Will
Put
Some
Lighting
Use
To
Give
You
A
Detailed
Introduction
First
Our
Software
The default
A light
The light that is opened
This is the original light in our light attribute
This is a light in our entire large environment
Then we click on the rendering
Then we open it
It will randomly perform a light rendering
There is an environment map here
You can see the attribute editor
There will be an environment map on the right
Then in our environment map
We can choose different software-based HDR files
After opening
It will change the effect of this light rendering
This is the lighting effect of our entire large environment
Our original light
The original light can only have one
Is the one on the far right of this row of lights
When we click on this button again
It will show that it is a skylight
The button below
Is where we can add a light
When we click
You can add a new light
First of all, it's our G-shaped light
When we click on the G-shaped light
It will be on the dot coordinates
To generate a G-shaped light
Then we can use the positioning ball at the 3D window
To move the position of this G-shaped light
The curve shows the direction of its reflection
Then we will manually turn off the light at the top of the circle
Convenient for everyone to check the effect of this G-shaped light
Then in order to show the effect of this G-shaped light
In order to make it more obvious
I will make a change to its intensity
Let's make it a little bigger
So that everyone can see it more clearly
Change it to 10 here
Then I click on the smoothing
Then everyone can see
Obviously see the effect of this G-shaped light
Just go straight from this light board
To emit such a light
The back of the light board is only shadow
Is black
Then I put this light board
Make a counter fire
In order to avoid affecting the light behind us
Next is our sphere lamp
The same sphere lamp
We use a light that is scattered
It doesn't have a specific direction
Then here I use the same intensity as the G-shaped lamp
Click on the smoothing
You can see that the picture will become very dark
That's because our sphere lamp
Its light is weaker
It's more gentle
It's more suitable to use to make up for the light
This is our sphere lamp
Then what we are going to talk about next
Is our spotlight
We open our spotlight
The same
We make a adjustment of a angle
The curve line represents one of its照射 directions
We can let it align with our clothing
Make a照射
Next, let's change our intensity
Just like before
Then do a smoothing
You can see that it appears
One of the effects of this kind of spotlight
Then we come to our hand-held editor
You can see that there is a corner angle here
We can adjust some of its values
The smallest angle
Is the angle of its light
After the adjustment
We can see that the light becomes very narrow
The larger the adjustment
Then the range of this light will be larger
The larger the reflection angle
The larger the light spread angle will be
The more soft it will be
Then the following is our shadow radius
The larger the shadow radius
The more the object shadow projected on the ground
The more soft it will be
Then this one
Is about us going to light a lamp
An explanation of a attribute setting
Then what's next
It's one of our purple lights
Then it will also be generated on our origin
Then we have a point of view of the purple light
Then we will make a setting
Then click on the following
You can see that this purple light
It's a
It's a completely parallel light
Then this light
It's a uniform light
He didn't say
Where does a light flash from
It's not a light flash
It's a completely parallel light
What about this light
It's to imitate the sun
It's an effect of a light flash
Then we can also change its color
Make a change
Of course, other colors can also be modified
Then we can change it to a lighter light yellow
Then after changing to light yellow
We can make a kind of dusk
Or a sunset effect
Then this is our purple light
Then what I'm going to talk about is our IES light
Then maybe you don't understand
It's not very clear
What is this IES?
What about IES?
It records the IES file of the real light data
Then we can use its IES file here
Then we first adjust the position of this IES light
Then we come to our
Adjust well
Our system will bring nine IES files
Then we can choose one by ourselves
This IES file
Different IES files will have a different lighting effect
Then we can put our front straight light
Turn it back on
Then do a rendering
Then we can see the effect of this IES light
The length of the light can be customized
A modification
Then we can make this intensity larger
We can make this effect more clear
That's all for us today
About our 5.2 new function live broadcast
Thank you all for watching
What questions do you have?
You can send it to me through the chat
Then I will make a reply
Do you have any questions?
You will see the answer in the comments
I see that there are people who say
Can the chain be separated from the belt and the tongue?
At present, we can't separate it
If you want to do this separation
Then you can only use your scan
To scan your real chain
Thank you.
If you want to have a thick layer, you need to increase the thickness of the thick layer.
Then make a thickness difference.
Will the 3D and actual clothes made by CLO look alike?
This is a prerequisite.
If you use a real fabric and a correct sewing technique,
the 3D clothing and a real sample will be 91% similar.
The 3D design is one of the most important aspects of the CLO.
Can the zipper be printed with the logo?
This question is about the logo.
It may require you to use a real fabric.
But it is not the 4D design.
It is a 3D design.
3D zipper function
If you want to use the board to make it
It's just like we normally do with clothing
Just add this sticker
And you're good to go
刚刚有人问,铭线可以导入其他三维软件吗?刚刚有人问,铭线可以导入其他三维软件吗?
那只要你鉴定了这个服装,然后上面有这个铭线的话 那只要你鉴定了这个服装,然后上面有这个铭线的话
那其实你把整个服装作为一个OBG导出去 那其实你把整个服装作为一个OBG导出去
那么在其他的3D软件里面也是可以进行一个读取的 那么在其他的3D软件里面也是可以进行一个读取的
那么在其他的3D软件里面也是可以进行一个读取的
We have also replied to the official website, which may be a little late.
In addition to the official website, you can also leave a message on our WeChat official account,
including our Weibo, you can also leave a message on it.
Our little sister, our little bacteria will also respond.
隐形拉链和防水拉链怎么弄好?
那隐形拉链的话呢,
如果说你不是要打开看里面的那个样子的话,
那你只需要正常的一个缝合,
然后在上面把隐形拉链的拉片放上去,
就以OBJ的形式,OBJ附件的形式放上去就可以了。
因为你正常隐形拉链的服装,
拉上拉链之后也是看不清里面的拉链的。
那如果你要拉开展示的话呢,
那么你可以做一个小板片,
细小的板片,然后把拉尺的一个纹理加进去。
在哪里可以下载到录播视频呢?
好,大家可以关注我们的微信公众号哦。
我们的微信公众号里面后面会放出我们的一个录播的。
哈哈哈哈,有人说你是不是Money,我告诉你我不是Money哦。
不对啊,我刚刚在前面就讲了,我是Samantha,你们有没有认真听的?
好,我们刚刚的小细菌做出了一个承诺,
你们的一个新功能的直播,
你们就可以看到Money了。
你们你的вор侄用 Snapdragon 802453D canvas ,
当然了它露不露脸的话我就不知道了。
你们可以催催。
boast of Furnace 4 Haiti.
Can I lock a board separately?
Yes, you can.
We just need to select this board and lock it.
Now, let's go to our page.
We select a single board.
Then right-click, we can see it.
We select a single board and right-click.
We can see that there is a lock on it.
We select lock.
We can select a single board and lock it.
Now, we have a single board.
We can see that there is a lock.
We mean that it is a lock.
刚刚有人问好工艺单能不能教一下好那工艺单呢是我们在
空塞上面的进行的一个自动生成的一个工艺单号那关于这个
口塞上面的使用了在后面我们会有一个专门的主题直播大家可以
关注一下大家可以多点问问题哦如果没有问题的话我们会在15分
结束的
有人问了一个问题说这个椅子扣里面有吗这个椅子扣里面没有
我们关于一些
OBJ的一些物件好像我们的台灯啊橱窗啊等等的这一些的我们是可以在其他的一个3D软件里面进行建模或者是呢在一些3D软3D的一个网站上面也会有很多的资源可以下载的那这一些只要是OBJ格式啊或者是FBX只要是我们软件支持的格式呢都可以导进来使用的
这个人口就是自动调oths
我们在Globe安装的那个 queremos想要的姓名标会的我承诺 current
我 burning
好
Can the model adjust the cup size of the chest alone?
Currently, we do not have such a function, but our model editor can set some data on the chest of our virtual model.
But this setting, I understand what you mean, may be thinking that when it is set, the data of other parts will not make any changes.
There may be some minor changes.
How to export 3D software?
Export 3D software.
You can export this costume as an OBJ file or FBX.
These files are exported.
We export the voice-over.
Drop an audio file.
We export the audio file.
We export the voice-over.
And we export the voice-over as well.
Like any other version of 3D software.
How do we export?
We export the voice-over to another language.
We export the audio to another language.
Next.
Let's use 4D sound and audio effects.
As you can see.
这个模特能不能分享啊,那这一个模特呢我们是不能够分享的哦,因为这个模特呢是,嗯,是不能分享。
嗯。
有人问能演绎一下导入的模特设置,
Let me open a model
Then we can open it
A combination point of an X-ray
A combination point
When we select the center
We can see the positioning ball
There is a symmetrical little man in the upper right corner
After we click
We can make a symmetrical position change
You can see that his hand can be opened symmetrically
If someone says that we have too little learning data
That's a lot of that
On our website
There will be an introduction to a lesson
Then on the Bilibili
We will also have a lot of teaching videos
You can watch it one by one
Of course we will also have a regular course live broadcast
If everyone pays attention
You can learn a lot of dry goods there
内字的模特贴图文,你能去掉内衣裤吗?
那当然这个是可以了啊
那在这里呢
OK,我现在再打开一个模特
那这个呢,因为现在是个直播,你懂的啊
我不会用我们的女模作为一个演示的
我们来打开一个男模啊
我们打开男模,VL的感觉好看一点
那我们打开男模之后呢
我们来到Tex
没有穿内裤的一个纹理的啊
那我们只需要点击模特的身体
然后来到我们的属性编辑器
就可以看到有这个纹理
那么我们把对应的这个纹理图好
没有穿的一个纹理图导进去就可以了
然后腿部这里呢
我们就要单独再点击腿部
然后把对应的腿部的纹理左键拖动
到纹理应用就可以了
来吧,这个线道就 drought 了
然后我们再点击Row
试一下这个线框
这边有一个纹理图
这个线框就是用来展示太平面的纹理图
a good way to place it can help you to improve the efficiency of this 3D clothing production
for example, we default clothing a way to place
the front piece of the back piece of the middle place to place the sleeves
that this is whether it is to sew or to adjust the
these操作呢都可以方便你
尽快的去找到你需要的摆片
那可以提高我们的工作效率
好大家还有什么问题吗
Thank you.
Okay, there's a person who has posted many chats.
You said it's not convenient to import three-dimensional software clothing materials.
What does it mean?
It's not the same as Clue.
This question might be a bit...
Is it the same in terms of texture or the same in terms of shape?
It's the same.
Let's see how to add a model to the rendering background.
Then let's go to our rendering window.
We'll move the rendering window to our rendering window.
We can see under our property editor,
we'll first choose a model of our video The kind of option and then there's a background under our ability to send the under the don't see one.
Let's open the researching inside.
Let's click on it.
open this
videmment explaining the following exercise here.
When you open the window, you can see some of the default files in the system.
You can choose one of them and open it.
You can also open your own folder and select your own physical image for an application.
Does the cherry blossom arrangement adjust the correct size of the flower?
Does it mean that your picture is not 1 to 1?
In order to see the effect of the flower,
it is best to use a 1 to 1 flower draft.
We can also choose the size of the flower draft.
Let's open one of the clothes.
Here we can see that if we use this cherry blossom,
here we can see that if we use this cherry blossom,
we will see a translation in our computer,
and there will be a text in the translation.
When you open the text, you can see the width and height of the text at the moment.
If the text size is different from your actual size, you can adjust it directly here.
Of course, the best effect is that you first make a 1-to-1 drawing and confirm that it is a quadrangle.
After that, it will be used in our software.
Thank you so much!
IES can be imported.
We just talked about it. We have a light. It's our IES light. After we select the IES light, we can see our
The
System brings its own IES file, so you can also import your own IES file
You can import your own IES file
and then insert it in the
So
让我们的HDR以及我们的IES文件都是从其他软件当中导进来的。
那大家还有什么问题吗?
嗯。
有人发了折信。
是折解的操作吧?
嗯。
the corresponding type of paper can be increased.
Do you have any questions?
Our live broadcast will end at 4.30.
Thank you.
Someone asked how to draw a rope.
There will be tutorials on our official website.
You can check it out.
Someone asked if we could do a live broadcast.
Please hurry up.
Our live broadcast is twice a month.
There will be more topics after this live broadcast.
You can pay more attention to it.
Maybe.
Maybe one day,
you will meet the right person.
Maybe.
If not,
I will be here any time.
If you meet the right person,
follow me.
See you.
Bye.
Uh...
Thank you.
See you.
See you later.
Bye.
How to tie a belt
There is a lot of posts on our official website about how to tie a belt.
You can pay attention to it.
Make sure you follow this website tolls us through tell us why we tie it.
If you can't tell us why you tied that belt, you can ask us.
The same thing.
Thank you.
Okay, if you don't have any more questions,
then our live broadcast today will end here.
Thank you, everyone.
I also hope you will pay attention to our basic course live broadcast at 8 p.m. tomorrow evening.
Thank you for your support today.
Thank you.